Good morning.
Just wondering if today we're ready to admit that the U.S. military was the IDF before the IDF.
Yeah.
I mean, whether we're talking Korea, Iraq, or any of the number of places where the U.S. military is stationed in 800 bases around the world.
If you have been in the military, you are a war criminal.
The United States is a war criminal.
Its whole existence is unknown.
And if you went into the military because you were trying to get money for school, they used you.
They did.
It's time to atone.
And then they be letting y'all board before the rest of us.
That's how committed they are to using y'all to carry out their terror.
Mm-hmm.
My ultimate goal is the liberation of my people.
We are of this land.